I broke down what it would cost for a
fan of last time's winners, Argentina,
to go to the first three matches on a
budget.
>> [music]
>> If they flew out of Buenos Aires to
Houston and then to Kansas City for the
first match,
and then flew to Dallas for matches two
and three,
flights and hotels alone would cost
about $7,000.
When I looked in May, the cheapest
[music] tickets I found on the resale
market for each of those three games
would cost about $747,
$835,
and $862. [music]
And using public transit in these cities
would be a combined $33.
Not too bad.
All in all, the Argentina fan would
shell out around $9,800.
Just for fun, I also calculated what an
Argentina fan would spend if they went
to every game from beginning to end.
Assuming the team makes it to the final
like last time, a fan would be looking
at about $31,250.
FIFA expects to bring in roughly $13
billion during this World Cup cycle,
making 2026 the most lucrative
tournament in its history. Meanwhile,
fans from many countries can't even
afford a single ticket, let alone the
travel costs.